Article Name	Simple Wikipedia Summary	Plain Wikipedia Summary	ID
Southwest Airlines Flight 1248	"Southwest Airlines Flight 1248 was a regularly-scheduled passenger flight from Baltimore to Chicago-Midway. On approach, the aircraft skid off the runway and into a street, killing a 6 year old boy in a car. It was the first fatal accident in the company's history."	"Southwest Airlines Flight 1248 (WN1248, SWA1248) was a scheduled passenger flight from Baltimore, Maryland, to Chicago, Illinois, to Salt Lake City, Utah, and then to Las Vegas, Nevada. On December 8, 2005, the airplane slid off a runway at Chicago-Midway while landing in a snowstorm and crashed into automobile traffic, killing a six-year-old boy."	0
"Norman Fowler, Baron Fowler"	"Peter Norman Fowler, Baron Fowler, PC (born 2 February 1938) is a British politician. He was a member of Margaret Thatcher's ministry. He is currently the Lord Speaker, having assumed office at the beginning of September 2016."	"Peter Norman Fowler, Baron Fowler  (born 2 February 1938) is a British politician who served as a member of both Margaret Thatcher and John Major's ministries during the 1980s and 1990s. He was elected Lord Speaker in September 2016."	1
Vera Glagoleva	"Vera Vitalievna Glagoleva (31 January 1956 – 16 August 2017) was a Russian actress. She was born in Moscow. She was known for her roles in Christmas movies or romantic comedies. Her best known roles were in Vyyti zamuzh za kapitana, Bednaya Sasha, and in Zhenshchin obizhat ne rekomenduyetsya. Glagoleva was awarded the People's Artist of Russia in 2011."	Vera Vitalievna Glagoleva (Russian: Ве́ра Вита́льевна Глаго́лева; 31 January 1956 – 16 August 2017) was a Russian actress and film director.	2
Andrzej Blumenfeld	"Andrzej Stanisław Blumenfeld (12 August 1951 – 14 August 2017) was a Polish actor and voice dubber. He was born in Zabrze, Poland. His career began in 1973. He was known for Polish-dubbing from American movies. His best known work are The Pianist, Delivery Man, and The Witcher."	"Andrzej Stanisław Blumenfeld (12 August 1951 in Zabrze – 14 August 2017 in Warsaw) was a Polish film, television, and voice actor who worked for SDI Media Polska."	3
Aharon Yadlin	"Aharon Yadlin (Hebrew: אהרן ידלין‎; born 17 April 1926) is a former Israeli educator and politician. He was born in Ben Shemen, Mandatory Palestine."	Aharon Yadlin (Hebrew: אהרן ידלין; born 17 April 1926) is a former Israeli educator and politician.	4
Eugenio Polgovsky	"Eugenio Polgovsky (June 29, 1977 – August 11, 2017) was a Mexican movie director, cinematographer and editor. He was born in Mexico City, Mexico. Polgovsky was known for the Mexican documentaries ""Tropic of Cancer"" ( Semaine de la Critique 2005) and  Los Herederos ""The Inheritors"" (Mostra of Venice, Orrizontti 2008 & Berlinale Generation 2009)."	"Eugenio Polgovsky (Mexico City, June 29, 1977 – London, August 11th, 2017) was a Mexican filmmaker and visual artist. He worked as director, cinematographer, editor, sound designer and producer of his films. Polgovsky was known for the Mexican documentaries ""Tropic of Cancer"" ( Semaine de la Critique 2005) and  Los Herederos ""The Inheritors"" (Mostra of Venice, Orrizontti 2008 & Berlinale Generation 2009)."	5
Vern Ehlers	"Vernon James ""Vern"" Ehlers (February 6, 1934 – August 15, 2017) was the former U.S. Representative for Michigan's 3rd congressional district, having served from 1993 until 2011. He was a member of the Republican Party."	"Vernon James Ehlers (February 6, 1934 – August 15, 2017) was an American physicist and politician who represented Michigan in the U.S. House of Representatives from 1993 until his retirement in 2011. A Republican, he also served eight years in the Michigan Senate and two in the Michigan House of Representatives."	6
Marie-Josephine Gaudette	"Marie-Josephine Clarice Gaudette (25 March 1902 – 13 July 2017) was an American-born Italian supercentenarian. She was the oldest living person in Italy from the death of Emma Morano, who was the oldest living person in the world and the oldest Italian person ever on 15 April 2017 until her own death three months later. "	"Italian supercentenarians are citizens, residents or emigrants from Italy who have attained or surpassed 110 years of age. As of January 2015, the Gerontology Research Group (GRG) had validated the longevity claims of 151 Italian supercentenarians. There are currently 12 known Italians alive over age 110; the oldest as of 26 June 2020 is Maria Oliva, born 16 April 1909, aged, 111 years, 71 days. The oldest Italian ever was Emma Morano, who was also the last person in the world to have been born before the year 1900. She died on 15 April 2017, aged 117 years and 137 days."	7
Sam Smith (singer)	"Samuel Frederick ""Sam"" Smith (born 19 May 1992) is a British singer-songwriter. They became famous in October 2012 when the song ""Latch"" by Disclosure came out. In 2013, they released the single ""Lay Me Down"". In 2014 Smith had a single, ""Stay with Me"" and ""Money on My Mind"" through their album In the Lonely Hour, which became a major international success. "	"Samuel Frederick Smith (born 19 May 1992) is an English singer and songwriter. They rose to prominence in October 2012 after being featured on Disclosure's breakthrough single ""Latch"", which peaked at number eleven on the UK Singles Chart. Smith was subsequently featured on Naughty Boy's ""La La La"", which became a number one single in May 2013. In December 2013, they were nominated for the 2014 Brit Critics' Choice Award and the BBC's Sound of 2014 poll, winning both.Smith's debut studio album, In the Lonely Hour, was released in May 2014 on Capitol Records UK. The album's lead single, ""Lay Me Down"", was released prior to ""La La La"". The album's second single, ""Money on My Mind"", became Smith's second number one single in the UK. The third single, ""Stay with Me"", was an international success, reaching number one in the UK and number two on the US Billboard Hot 100, while their singles ""I'm Not the Only One"" and ""Like I Can"" reached the top ten in the UK. The album won four awards, at the 57th Annual Grammy Awards, including Best Pop Vocal Album, Best New Artist, Record of the Year, Song of the Year, and nominations for Album of the Year and Best Pop Solo Performance."	8
Hans Streuli	Hans Streuli (13 July 1892 – 23 May 1970) was a Swiss politician.	Hans Streuli (13 July 1892 – 23 May 1970) was a Swiss politician.	9
Orthodox Jew	"Orthodox Judaism is the more traditional form of nowadays Judaism. It holds that both the scripture of the Torah and mouth-to-mouth traditions later written down in the Talmud etc., were actually and literally given by God, and that past rabbis handed them over without change and were always faithful in deciding how they applied to reality. Because of this, Orthodox Judaism is very careful in holding to the tradition of past rabbis, and is very conservative on how current rabbis may decide what the law is in new cases. Orthodox Jews consider themselves as the only truly faithful Jews and reject all the new non-Orthodox forms of Jewish thought, religious or secular, that came to be in the last 250 years (since the Jewish community lost its powers to enforce people, and Jews began to be citizens of the modern state). Even so, they are a product of new times just like everyone else: Their community organizations were created so they could separate from other Jews because those stopped being religious. The Orthodox also had to make very new ways of thinking and acting to deal with the big changes.   "	"Orthodox Judaism is a collective term for the traditionalist branches of contemporary Rabbinic Judaism. Theologically, it is chiefly defined by regarding the Torah, both Written and Oral, as literally revealed by God on Mount Sinai and faithfully transmitted ever since."	10
Fritz Honegger	Fritz Honegger (25 July 1917 – 4 March 1999) was a Swiss politician.	Fritz Honegger (25 July 1917 – 4 March 1999) was a Swiss politician.	11
Fuldera	Fuldera is a village and former municipality of the district of Inn in the canton of Graubünden in Switzerland.	"Fuldera is a village in the Val Müstair municipality in the district of Inn in the Swiss canton of Graubünden.  In 2009 Fuldera merged with Lü, Müstair, Santa Maria Val Müstair, Tschierv and Valchava to form the municipality of Val Müstair."	12
Fadwa Soliman	"Fadwa Soliman or Fadwa Suleiman (17 May 1970 – 17 August 2017) was a Syrian actress and activist. She was born in Aleppo, Syria. She led a Sunni-majority protest against Bashar al-Assad's government in Homs. She became one of the most recognized faces of the Syrian Civil War.On 17 August 2017 Soliman died of cancer while in exile in Paris, aged 47."	Fadwa Souleimane (also transcribed as Fadwa Soliman or Fadwa Suleiman; 17 May 1970 – 17 August 2017) was a Syrian actress of Alawite descent who led a Sunni-majority protest against Bashar al-Assad's government in Homs. She became one of the most recognized faces of the Syrian Civil War.	13
2017 Barcelona attack	"On 17 August 2017, a white van hit pedestrians on La Rambla, Barcelona, leaving fourteen people dead and dozens injured. The two suspects then fled on foot.At around 17:20 CEST, a white Fiat Talento drove onto the pavement of Barcelona's Las Ramblas, crashing into pedestrians between Plaça Catalunya and Gran Teatre del Liceu.In the press conference held by the police at 7:00pm local time, the spokesperson confirmed the terrorist nature of the event, a dead person and 32 injured —10 of those in serious condition.  Other sources are claiming the fatality count is 13.Police said two men were arrested in connection with the attack; another was reported killed in a shootout with police. In Ripoll, a man in his 20s was alleged to have rented the van, but told police his ID was stolen. Amaq News Agency said the attackers were ""soldiers of the Islamic State"" who ""carried out the operation in response to calls for targeting coalition states"".An explosion happened the night before the attack in the Catalan town of Alcanar. It flattened a building and killed a woman. The head of the Mossos d'Esquadra Josep Lluís Trapero said it was related to the ramming. Nine hours after the attack, police killed four people in Tarragona said to be planning a terrorist attack in Cambrils."	"On the afternoon of 17 August 2017, 22-year-old Younes Abouyaaqoub drove a van into pedestrians on La Rambla in Barcelona, Catalonia, Spain killing 13 people and injuring at least 130 others, one of whom died 10 days later on 27 August. Abouyaaqoub fled the attack on foot, then killed another person in order to steal the victim's car to make his escape.Nine hours after the Barcelona attack, five men thought to be members of the same terrorist cell drove into pedestrians in nearby Cambrils, killing one woman and injuring six others. All five of those attackers were shot and killed by police.The night before the Barcelona attack, an explosion occurred in a house in the Spanish town of Alcanar, destroying the building and killing two members of the terrorist cell, including the 40-year-old imam thought to be the mastermind. The home had more than 120 gas canisters inside which police believe the cell was attempting to make into one large bomb (or three smaller bombs to be placed in three vans which they had rented) but which they accidentally detonated.The Prime Minister of Spain, Mariano Rajoy, called the attack in Barcelona a jihadist attack. Amaq News Agency attributed indirect responsibility for the attack to the Islamic State of Iraq and the Levant (ISIL). The attacks were the deadliest in Spain since the March 2004 Madrid train bombings and the deadliest in Barcelona since the 1987 Hipercor bombing. Younes Abouyaaqoub, the driver of the van in the Barcelona attack, was killed by police in a town 30 miles west of Barcelona on 21 August."	14
Grentzingen	"Grentzingen is a former commune. It is found in the Haut-Rhin department of eastern France. On 1 January 2016, it was merged into the new commune of Illtal.It is 25 km west of Basel and 10 km southeast of Altkirch."	"Grentzingen (German: Grenzingen) is a former commune in the Haut-Rhin department in north-eastern France. On 1 January 2016, it was merged into the new commune Illtal."	15
Griesbach-au-Val	Griesbach-au-Val is a commune. It is found in the Haut-Rhin department of eastern France.	Griesbach-au-Val (German: Griesbach im Thal) is a commune in the Haut-Rhin department in Grand Est in north-eastern France.	16
Grussenheim	Grussenheim is a commune. It is found in the Haut-Rhin department of eastern France.	Grussenheim (German: Grüssenheim) is a commune in the Haut-Rhin department in Grand Est in north-eastern France.	17
Viaur	"The Viaur is a river in southern France, left tributary of the Aveyron river. It flows through the Aveyron, Tarn and Tarn-et-Garonne departments."	"The Viaur is a 168 km (104 mi) long river in south-western France. It is a left tributary of the Aveyron. Its source is in the southern Massif Central, north of Millau. It flows generally west through the following departments and towns:"	18
M. T. Liggett	"Myron Thomas ""M. T."" Liggett (December 28, 1930 – August 17, 2017) was an American folk sculptor. He was born near Mullinville, Kansas. He exhibited hundreds of his artworks on the roads of Mullinville. "	"Myron Thomas Liggett (December 28, 1930 – August 17, 2017) was an American folk sculptor.Liggett was born in Mullinville, Kansas and grew up on his family farm. He graduated from Mullinville High School. Liggett went to Dodge City Community College. He also went to the University of Texas where he majored in political science. Liggett served in the United States Navy in 1948 and then joined the United States Air Force in 1957. In 1987, Liggett returned to Mullinville, Kansas where he exhibited his art work containing re-used farm implements, welded metal and combined discs. His works were kinetic and moved with the wind. He received his bachelor's degree from Fort Hays State University and went to the University of Nevada, Las Vegas law school.M. T. Liggett's main venue was the land along his front fence, on the north side of U.S. Route 400 in Mullinville. He was also a featured artist at the Folk Art Museum in Lucas, Kansas.He and some of his sculptures appear in the 2009 documentary What's the Matter with Kansas?.Liggett died on August 17, 2017 at the age of 86 at Wesley Medical Center in Wichita, Kansas."	19
John Boorman	"John Boorman (; born 18 January 1933) is an English filmmaker.Boorman is best known for his feature movies such as Point Blank, Hell in the Pacific, Leo the Last, Deliverance, Zardoz, Excalibur, The Emerald Forest, Hope and Glory, The General, The Tailor of Panama, and Queen and Country. "	"John Boorman ,  (born 18 January 1933) is an English filmmaker who is best known for his feature films such as Point Blank, Hell in the Pacific, Deliverance, Zardoz, Exorcist II: The Heretic, Excalibur, The Emerald Forest, Hope and Glory, The General, The Tailor of Panama and Queen and Country."	20
George Edward Glass	"George Edward Glass is an American businessman and diplomat. He has been confirmed by the United States Senate as the next United States Ambassador to Portugal. This nomination was confirmed by the U.S. Senate on August 3, 2017. He took office on August 25, 2017."	"George Edward Glass (born August 27, 1960) is an American businessman and diplomat.  He currently serves as the Ambassador of the United States to the Republic of Portugal."	21
Duke Buchan	"Richard Duke Buchan III (born July 3, 1963) is an American entrepreneur, financier, farmer, and philanthropist. He is the founder and CEO of Hunter Global Investors, a private investment management firm.Buchan has been nominated by President Donald Trump to become United States Ambassador to Spain and Andorra. This nomination was confirmed by the United States Senate on November 2, 2017."	"Richard Duke Buchan III (born July 3, 1963) is the United States Ambassador to Spain and Andorra. On November 2, 2017 Buchan was confirmed by the United States Senate by voice vote. He was sworn in by Vice President Mike Pence on December 11, 2017. Buchan is an American entrepreneur, financier, farmer, and philanthropist. He is the founder and CEO of Hunter Global Investors, a private investment management firm."	22
Pete Hoekstra	"Pieter ""Pete"" Hoekstra (; born October 30, 1953) is an American politician of Dutch descent. He is the United States Ambassador to the Netherlands since November 2017. He is a former member of the United States House of Representatives, representing Michigan's 2nd congressional district from 1993 to 2011. Hoekstra is a member of the Republican Party."	"Cornelis Pieter ""Pete"" Hoekstra (; born October 30, 1953) is a Dutch-American politician serving as the United States Ambassador to the Netherlands since January 10, 2018. A member of the Republican Party, he previously served as the U.S. Representative for Michigan's 2nd congressional district from 1993 to 2011."	23
Jamie McCourt	"Jamie D. McCourt (born December 5, 1953) is a businesswoman and investor. She is the founder and CEO of Jamie Enterprises, and the former co-owner and executive of the Los Angeles Dodgers. She became the highest-ranking woman in Major League Baseball, appointed first as Vice Chairman of the Dodgers in 2004, then President in 2005, and finally CEO in 2009. On June 22, 2017, she was nominated as United States Ambassador to Belgium.On August 2, 2017, President Trump formally withdrew her nomination and instead nominated her as United States Ambassador to France and United States Ambassador to Monaco. This nomination was confirmed by the United States Senate on November 2, 2017."	"Jamie D. McCourt (née Luskin; born December 5, 1953) is the United States Ambassador to the French Republic and Principality of Monaco. She was confirmed by the Senate and sworn in on November 2, 2017. Ambassador McCourt is also the United States Permanent Observer to the Council of Europe. McCourt is the founder and CEO of Jamie Enterprises and a former executive of the Los Angeles Dodgers. She became the highest-ranking woman in Major League Baseball, appointed first as vice chairman of the Dodgers in 2004, then President in 2005, and finally CEO in 2009."	24
Steve King (businessman)	"Steve King (born July 4, 1941) is an American businessman and Republican Party activist. He is the founder of King Capital LLC, an equity investment and real estate company. He is a former FBI agent.In 1988, he campaigned unsuccessfully for the Republican U.S. Senate nomination in Wisconsin.In July 2017, President Donald Trump nominated King to be the next United States Ambassador to the Czech Republic. This nomination was confirmed by the U.S. Senate on October 5, 2017."	"Stephen B. King (born July 4, 1941) is an American businessman and political activist serving as the United States Ambassador to the Czech Republic since 2017. A member of the Republican Party, he is the founder of King Capital LLC, an equity investment and real estate company. He previously worked at the Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI) as an agent and campaigned unsuccessfully in 1988 for his party's nomination for the U.S. Senate in Wisconsin."	25
Sharon Day	"Sharon Day is an American politician. She is the former co-chairwoman of the Republican National Committee.On August 3, 2017, she was confirmed as the next United States Ambassador to Costa Rica. She was nominated by President Donald Trump. She took office on September 25, 2017."	Sharon Day is the United States Ambassador to Costa Rica. She previously served as the co-chairwoman of the Republican National Committee.	26
Kelly Knight Craft	"Kelly Dawn Knight Craft (née Guilfoil; born February 24, 1962) is an American diplomat. She is the 30th and current United States Ambassador to the United Nations since September 2019. Before, she was the United States ambassador to Canada, the first woman to hold the post.In 2007, she was appointed by President George W. Bush as the U.S. delegate to the United Nations, where her focus included U.S. engagement in Africa. Knight-Craft was a delegate to the 2016 Republican National Convention from Kentucky. She is a member of the University of Kentucky's board of directors. She heads Kelly G. Knight LLC, a business advisory firm based in Lexington, Kentucky."	"Kelly Dawn Craft (née Guilfoil; born February 24, 1962) is an American diplomat who currently serves as the United States Ambassador to the United Nations. Craft previously served as the United States ambassador to Canada, being the first woman to hold the office. She was appointed by President George W. Bush as a U.S. alternate delegate to the United Nations in 2007, where her focus included U.S. engagement in Africa. She was a delegate to the 2016 Republican National Convention from Kentucky. She headed Kelly G. Knight LLC, a business advisory firm based in Lexington, Kentucky.She was confirmed by the U.S. Senate in a vote of 56-34, and was officially sworn in as the United Nations Ambassador on September 10, 2019. She formally presented her credentials to Secretary-General António Guterres on September 12, 2019."	27
Doug Manchester	"Douglas Frederick ""Doug"" Manchester (born June 3, 1942) is an American businessman and philanthropist. He is the former chairman of Manchester Financial Group, past chairman and publisher of The San Diego Union-Tribune. He is the nominee to become United States Ambassador to the Bahamas.Manchester has built some of the tallest hotels and office buildings in San Diego, including the San Diego Marriott Marquis & Marina and the Manchester Grand Hyatt, and is credited as a driving force behind the development of the San Diego Convention Center. Manchester also built the triple 5-star Grand Del Mar Resort & Spa, which sold to Fairmont Hotels & Resorts in 2015, and he maintains a minority ownership.Manchester built the Torrey Executive Centre, Manchester Financial Building, Whitetail Lodge and Golf Club, and is currently building the Fairmont Austin hotel in Austin, Texas."	"Douglas Frederick Manchester (born June 3, 1942) is an American businessman and philanthropist. He is the former chairman of Manchester Financial Group, past chairman and publisher of The San Diego Union-Tribune, and an unsuccessful nominee to become United States Ambassador to the Bahamas. Manchester, who prefers to be called ""Papa Doug"", has built some of the tallest hotels and office buildings in San Diego, including the San Diego Marriott Marquis & Marina and the Manchester Grand Hyatt, and is credited as a driving force behind the development of the San Diego Convention Center. Manchester also built the triple 5-star Grand Del Mar Resort & Spa, which was sold to Fairmont Hotels & Resorts in 2015, and he maintains a minority ownership. Manchester also built the Torrey Executive Centre, Manchester Financial Building, Whitetail Lodge and Golf Club, Fairmont Austin and is currently building the Manchester Pacific Gateway.Manchester has long been involved in conservative politics and with the Republican Party. In late 2019, the Republican National Committee cut all ties with Manchester after CBS News obtained emails between Manchester, Ronna McDaniel, and GOP senate staffers in which Manchester appeared to be engaged in a pay-to-play scheme."	28
John R. Bass	"John R. Bass (born 1964) is an American diplomat. He is the current United States Ambassador to Afghanistan since December 2017. He served as the United States Ambassador to Turkey from 2014 to 2016. He was United States Ambassador to Georgia from 2009 to 2012.President Donald Trump named him as his choice to become the United States Ambassador to Afghanistan on July 20, 2017. On September 28, 2017, his nomination was confirmed by the Senate."	"John Rodney Bass II (born 1964) is an American diplomat, who served as the United States Ambassador to Afghanistan from 2017 to 2020. He was the U.S. ambassador to Turkey 2014–2017 and the U.S. ambassador to Georgia 2009–2012."	29
Jeffrey Dean Morgan	"Jeffrey Dean Morgan (born April 22, 1966) is an American actor. He is known for playing John Winchester on Supernatural, Denny Duquette on the medical drama Grey's Anatomy, The Comedian in the 2009 superhero movie Watchmen, Jason Crouse on The Good Wife, and Negan on The Walking Dead. "	"Jeffrey Dean Morgan is an American actor of film and television. He is known for his roles as John Winchester in the fantasy horror series Supernatural (2005–2007; 2019), Denny Duquette in the medical drama series Grey's Anatomy (2006–2009), the Comedian in the superhero film Watchmen (2009), Jason Crouse in the political drama series The Good Wife (2015–2016), Negan in the horror drama series The Walking Dead (2016–present), and Harvey Russell in Rampage (2018)."	30
Lauren Cohan	"Lauren Cohan (born January 7, 1982) is a British American actress and model.Cohan best known for her role as Maggie Rhee on The Walking Dead (2011–present). She is also known for her recurring roles on the television series Supernatural (2007–2008), Chuck (2011) and The Vampire Diaries (2010–2012), and in the comedy movie Van Wilder: The Rise of Taj (2006), the psychological thriller The Boy, and for her role in the DC Extended Universe as character Martha Wayne in Batman v Superman: Dawn of Justice (2016)."	"Lauren Cohan (born January 7, 1982) is an American–English actress best known for her role as Maggie Greene in the horror television series The Walking Dead (2011–2018, 2020). Her other notable TV roles include Bela Talbot in the fantasy-horror series Supernatural (2007–2008), Rose in the supernatural series The Vampire Diaries (2010–2012), Vivian McArthur Volkoff in the action comedy series Chuck (2007), and  Francesca 'Frankie' Trowbridge in the spy drama Whiskey Cavalier (2019). Her film appearances include the comedy Van Wilder: The Rise of Taj (2006), the psychological thriller horror The Boy (2016), the biographical drama All Eyez on Me (2017), and the action thriller Mile 22 (2018)."	31
Ben Ferencz	"Benjamin Berell Ferencz (born March 11, 1920) is a Romanian-born American lawyer of Hungarian-Jewish descent. He was an investigator of Nazi war crimes after World War II and the Chief Prosecutor for the United States Army at the Einsatzgruppen Trial, one of the twelve military trials held by the U.S. authorities at Nuremberg, Germany."	"Benjamin Berell Ferencz (born March 11, 1920) is an American lawyer. He was an investigator of Nazi war crimes after World War II and the chief prosecutor for the United States Army at the Einsatzgruppen Trial, one of the 12 military trials held by the U.S. authorities at Nuremberg, Germany. Later, he became an advocate of the establishment of an international rule of law and of an International Criminal Court. From 1985 to 1996, he was adjunct professor of international law at Pace University."	32
Benjamin Ferencz	"Benjamin Berell Ferencz (born March 11, 1920) is a Romanian-born American lawyer of Hungarian-Jewish descent. He was an investigator of Nazi war crimes after World War II and the Chief Prosecutor for the United States Army at the Einsatzgruppen Trial, one of the twelve military trials held by the U.S. authorities at Nuremberg, Germany."	"Benjamin Berell Ferencz (born March 11, 1920) is an American lawyer. He was an investigator of Nazi war crimes after World War II and the chief prosecutor for the United States Army at the Einsatzgruppen Trial, one of the 12 military trials held by the U.S. authorities at Nuremberg, Germany. Later, he became an advocate of the establishment of an international rule of law and of an International Criminal Court. From 1985 to 1996, he was adjunct professor of international law at Pace University."	33
Stanislav Lyubshin	"Stanislav Andreyevich Lyubshin (Russian: Станисла́в Андре́евич Любшин; born 6 April 1933) is a Russian actor, screenwriter and movie director. He was awarded the People's Artist of the RSFSR in 1981. His debut movie was Shchit i mech (1968). From 1964 to 1967, he was member of the Taganka Theatre company in Moscow. Since 1981 Lyubshin has been permanent member with the Moscow Art Theatre (MKhAT named after A. Chekhov)."	"Stanislav Andreyevich Lyubshin (Russian: Станислав Андреевич Любшин; born 6 April 1933) is a Russian actor, film director, and People's Artist of the RSFSR (1981)."	34
Eberhard Jäckel	"Eberhard Jäckel (June 29, 1929 – August 15, 2017) was a Social Democratic German historian. He was known for his studies of Adolf Hitler's role in German history. Jäckel sees Hitler as being the historical equivalent to the Chernobyl disaster."	"Eberhard Jäckel (29 June 1929 – 15 August 2017) was a Social Democratic German historian, noted for his studies of Adolf Hitler's role in German history. Jäckel sees Hitler as being the historical equivalent to the Chernobyl disaster."	35
Gueberschwihr	Gueberschwihr is a commune. It is found in the Haut-Rhin department of eastern France.	Gueberschwihr (Alemannic German: Gawerschwihr; German: Geberschweier) is a commune in the Haut-Rhin department in Grand Est in north-eastern France.	36
Citroën Jumpy	The Citroën Jumpy (Citroën Dispatch in some countries) is a series of vans and passenger vans produced by Citroën in three generations since 1994. It is builded in cooperation with Fiat and Peugeot.	The Citroën Jumpy (badged Citroën Dispatch in some countries) is a light commercial van produced at Sevel Nord since 1994. The Jumpy was also sold as the Peugeot Expert and Fiat Scudo beginning in 1995.	37
Citroen Jumpy	The Citroën Jumpy (Citroën Dispatch in some countries) is a series of vans and passenger vans produced by Citroën in three generations since 1994. It is builded in cooperation with Fiat and Peugeot.	The Citroën Jumpy (badged Citroën Dispatch in some countries) is a light commercial van produced at Sevel Nord since 1994. The Jumpy was also sold as the Peugeot Expert and Fiat Scudo beginning in 1995.	38
Citroen Space Tourer	The Citroën Jumpy (Citroën Dispatch in some countries) is a series of vans and passenger vans produced by Citroën in three generations since 1994. It is builded in cooperation with Fiat and Peugeot.	The Citroën Jumpy (badged Citroën Dispatch in some countries) is a light commercial van produced at Sevel Nord since 1994. The Jumpy was also sold as the Peugeot Expert and Fiat Scudo beginning in 1995.	39
Citroen Spacetourer	The Citroën Jumpy (Citroën Dispatch in some countries) is a series of vans and passenger vans produced by Citroën in three generations since 1994. It is builded in cooperation with Fiat and Peugeot.	The Citroën Jumpy (badged Citroën Dispatch in some countries) is a light commercial van produced at Sevel Nord since 1994. The Jumpy was also sold as the Peugeot Expert and Fiat Scudo beginning in 1995.	40
Citroen Dispatch	The Citroën Jumpy (Citroën Dispatch in some countries) is a series of vans and passenger vans produced by Citroën in three generations since 1994. It is builded in cooperation with Fiat and Peugeot.	The Citroën Jumpy (badged Citroën Dispatch in some countries) is a light commercial van produced at Sevel Nord since 1994. The Jumpy was also sold as the Peugeot Expert and Fiat Scudo beginning in 1995.	41
Citroën Dispatch	The Citroën Jumpy (Citroën Dispatch in some countries) is a series of vans and passenger vans produced by Citroën in three generations since 1994. It is builded in cooperation with Fiat and Peugeot.	The Citroën Jumpy (badged Citroën Dispatch in some countries) is a light commercial van produced at Sevel Nord since 1994. The Jumpy was also sold as the Peugeot Expert and Fiat Scudo beginning in 1995.	42
Citroën Space Tourer	The Citroën Jumpy (Citroën Dispatch in some countries) is a series of vans and passenger vans produced by Citroën in three generations since 1994. It is builded in cooperation with Fiat and Peugeot.	The Citroën Jumpy (badged Citroën Dispatch in some countries) is a light commercial van produced at Sevel Nord since 1994. The Jumpy was also sold as the Peugeot Expert and Fiat Scudo beginning in 1995.	43
Citroën Spacetourer	The Citroën Jumpy (Citroën Dispatch in some countries) is a series of vans and passenger vans produced by Citroën in three generations since 1994. It is builded in cooperation with Fiat and Peugeot.	The Citroën Jumpy (badged Citroën Dispatch in some countries) is a light commercial van produced at Sevel Nord since 1994. The Jumpy was also sold as the Peugeot Expert and Fiat Scudo beginning in 1995.	44
Citroёn Space Tourer	The Citroën Jumpy (Citroën Dispatch in some countries) is a series of vans and passenger vans produced by Citroën in three generations since 1994. It is builded in cooperation with Fiat and Peugeot.	The Citroën Jumpy (badged Citroën Dispatch in some countries) is a light commercial van produced at Sevel Nord since 1994. The Jumpy was also sold as the Peugeot Expert and Fiat Scudo beginning in 1995.	45
Peugeot Expert	The Citroën Jumpy (Citroën Dispatch in some countries) is a series of vans and passenger vans produced by Citroën in three generations since 1994. It is builded in cooperation with Fiat and Peugeot.	The Citroën Jumpy (badged Citroën Dispatch in some countries) is a light commercial van produced at Sevel Nord since 1994. The Jumpy was also sold as the Peugeot Expert and Fiat Scudo beginning in 1995.	46
Peugeot Expert Tepee	The Citroën Jumpy (Citroën Dispatch in some countries) is a series of vans and passenger vans produced by Citroën in three generations since 1994. It is builded in cooperation with Fiat and Peugeot.	The Citroën Jumpy (badged Citroën Dispatch in some countries) is a light commercial van produced at Sevel Nord since 1994. The Jumpy was also sold as the Peugeot Expert and Fiat Scudo beginning in 1995.	47
Peugeot Traveller	The Citroën Jumpy (Citroën Dispatch in some countries) is a series of vans and passenger vans produced by Citroën in three generations since 1994. It is builded in cooperation with Fiat and Peugeot.	The Citroën Jumpy (badged Citroën Dispatch in some countries) is a light commercial van produced at Sevel Nord since 1994. The Jumpy was also sold as the Peugeot Expert and Fiat Scudo beginning in 1995.	48
Toyota ProAce	The Citroën Jumpy (Citroën Dispatch in some countries) is a series of vans and passenger vans produced by Citroën in three generations since 1994. It is builded in cooperation with Fiat and Peugeot.	The Citroën Jumpy (badged Citroën Dispatch in some countries) is a light commercial van produced at Sevel Nord since 1994. The Jumpy was also sold as the Peugeot Expert and Fiat Scudo beginning in 1995.	49
Toyota Proace	The Citroën Jumpy (Citroën Dispatch in some countries) is a series of vans and passenger vans produced by Citroën in three generations since 1994. It is builded in cooperation with Fiat and Peugeot.	The Citroën Jumpy (badged Citroën Dispatch in some countries) is a light commercial van produced at Sevel Nord since 1994. The Jumpy was also sold as the Peugeot Expert and Fiat Scudo beginning in 1995.	50
Sonny Landham	"William M. ""Sonny"" Landham (February 11, 1941 – August 17, 2017) was an American actor, stunt man and politician. He played tracker Billy Sole in the action movie Predator.Landham was born in Canton, Georgia. He studied at the University of Georgia."	"William M. ""Sonny"" Landham (February 11, 1941 – August 17, 2017) was an American film actor and stunt man. He portrayed Billy Bear in 48 Hrs. and tracker Billy Sole in Predator."	51
Krestovsky Stadium	"The Saint Petersburg Stadium (Russian: Стадион Санкт-Петербург; also called the Krestovsky Stadium or Zenit Arena) is an association football stadium in Saint Petersburg, Russia. During the  2018 FIFA World Cup, the stadium had a capacity of 64,468 people. The stadium cost $1.1 billion to $1.4 billion.The stadium is now the home of FC Zenit St. Petersburg. It was used for the 2017 FIFA Confederations Cup, 2018 FIFA World Cup, and will be used for the UEFA Euro 2020."	"Krestovsky Stadium, known as Gazprom Arena for sponsorship reasons, (Russian: «Газпром Арена») is a retractable roof stadium with a retractable pitch in the western portion of Krestovsky Island in Saint Petersburg, Russia, which serves as home for FC Zenit Saint Petersburg. The stadium was opened in 2017 for the FIFA Confederations Cup. It was called Saint Petersburg Stadium during the 2017 FIFA Confederations Cup and 2018 FIFA World Cup."	52
Black-body radiation	"Blackbody radiation is radiation produced by heated objects, particularly from a blackbody. A blackbody is an object that absorbs all radiation (visible light, infrared light, ultraviolet light, etc.) that falls on it. This also means that it will also radiate at all frequencies that heat energy produces in it."	"Black-body radiation is the thermal electromagnetic radiation within or surrounding a body in thermodynamic equilibrium with its environment, emitted by a black body (an idealized opaque, non-reflective body).  It has a specific spectrum of wavelengths, inversely related to intensity that depend only on the body's temperature, which is assumed for the sake of calculations and theory to be uniform and constant.The thermal radiation spontaneously emitted by many ordinary objects can be approximated as black-body radiation.  A perfectly insulated enclosure that is in thermal equilibrium internally contains black-body radiation and will emit it through a hole made in its wall, provided the hole is small enough to have a negligible effect upon the equilibrium."	53
Abdirahman Jama Barre	"Abdirahman Jama Barre (Somali: Cabdiraxmaan Jaamac Barre, Arabic: عبد الرحمن جامع بري‎‎) (1937 – 15 August 2017) was a Somali politician. He twice served as the Minister of Foreign Affairs of the Somali Democratic Republic, and later as the Minister of Finance. He was also the 1st Deputy Prime Minister of Somalia. He served all three positions at the same time from 1987 through 1991. "	"Abdirahman Jama Barre (Somali: Cabdiraxmaan Jaamac Barre, Arabic: عبد الرحمن جامع بري‎) (1937 – 15 August 2017) was a Somali politician. He twice served as the Minister of Foreign Affairs of the Somali Democratic Republic, and later as the Minister of Finance. He was also the 1st Deputy Prime Minister of Somalia."	54
Laurie Brokenshire	"Commodore Laurence Phillip Brokenshire CBE, RN (20 October 1952 – 4 August 2017) was a British navy officer and magician. He was born in Plymouth, Devon. He studied at the University of Exeter. His career developed as a submariner and later as a senior Royal Navy officer. He retired as officer in 2003. Laurie was accepted into the Inner Magic Circle, and became an occasional professional / semi-professional magic performer."	"Commodore Laurence Phillip Brokenshire CBE (1952–2017), known as Laurie Brokenshire, was a Royal Naval officer, magician and world-class puzzle solver."	55
Pertti Alaja	"Pertti Johannes Alaja (18 February 1952 – 18 August 2017) was a Finnish footballer. He was born in Helsinki, Finland. He played as a goalkeeper. He played for HJK, Haka, Oulun Työväen Palloilijat, Ikast, Edmonton Drillers, Malmö FF and for the Finland national football team.Alaja was elected as the 15th president of the Football Association of Finland on 14 October 2012, replacing Sauli Niinistö.Alaja died in Espoo, Finland, on 18 August 2017 of cancer at the age of 65."	"Pertti Johannes Alaja (18 February 1952 – 18 August 2017) was a Finnish footballer who played as a goalkeeper.Alaja was elected as the 15th president of the Football Association of Finland on 14 October 2012, replacing Sauli Niinistö."	56
2017 Turku stabbings	"On 18 August 2017, around 16:00 local time (UTC+3), several people were stabbed in central Turku, Finland. Alarm was first raised at 16:02 and by 16:05 the suspect had been captured. At least two people died in the attack."	"The 2017 Turku attack took place on 18 August 2017 at around 16:02–16:05 local time (UTC+3) when 10 people were stabbed in central Turku, Southwest Finland. Two women were killed in the attack and eight people sustained injuries. It remains the only terrorist attack ever in Finland.Police were informed at 16:02. Three minutes later the attacker, Abderrahman Bouanane, a Moroccan rejected asylum seeker, had been detained. At the time of his arrest, Bouanane was using the name Abderrahman Mechkah, which was later discovered to be a false identity. In June 2018, Bouanane was found guilty of two counts of murder with terrorist intent and eight counts of attempted murder with terrorist intent. It was the first time anybody had been sentenced for a terrorist crime in Finland."	57
2017 Turku stabbing	"On 18 August 2017, around 16:00 local time (UTC+3), several people were stabbed in central Turku, Finland. Alarm was first raised at 16:02 and by 16:05 the suspect had been captured. At least two people died in the attack."	"The 2017 Turku attack took place on 18 August 2017 at around 16:02–16:05 local time (UTC+3) when 10 people were stabbed in central Turku, Southwest Finland. Two women were killed in the attack and eight people sustained injuries. It remains the only terrorist attack ever in Finland.Police were informed at 16:02. Three minutes later the attacker, Abderrahman Bouanane, a Moroccan rejected asylum seeker, had been detained. At the time of his arrest, Bouanane was using the name Abderrahman Mechkah, which was later discovered to be a false identity. In June 2018, Bouanane was found guilty of two counts of murder with terrorist intent and eight counts of attempted murder with terrorist intent. It was the first time anybody had been sentenced for a terrorist crime in Finland."	58
Sapa'u Ruperake Petaia	Sapa'u Ruperake Petaia (born 11 April 1951) is a Samoan poet and writer. 	"Sapa'u Ruperake Petaia (born 11 April 1951) is a poet and writer from Samoa. His poem Blue Rain became the title of a collection of his poems first published in 1980 with later editions in the 1990s. The collection included the satirical poem Kidnapped (1974) which explores themes about the loss of traditional Samoan knowledge. Like other Samoan writers such as Albert Wendt, Petaia's work explores themes about the effects of colonialism and Western influences on Samoan culture and society.Petaia was born in Samoa. He attended Samoa College and worked as a clerk in the Public Service Commission in 1973. In 1978 he won a government scholarship to study at the University of the South Pacific in Fiji."	59
Herman Mandui	"Herman Mandui (1969 - October 4, 2014) was an archaeologist from Papua New Guinea."	"Herman Mandui (1969 – October 4, 2014) was a Papua New Guinean archaeologist. He served as the Chief Archaeologist of Papua New Guinea starting in 2008 until his death in 2014. He has been regarded as a ""pioneer of archeological research"" in Papua New Guinea, having worked on such sites as the Kuk Swamp in Western Highlands Province and the early human settlement sites in the Ivane Valley of the Goilala District."	60
Daniel Catan	"Daniel Catán Porteny (3 April 1949 in Mexico City - 9 April 2011 in Austin, Texas) was a Mexican opera composer of Jewish descent. He is best known for turning the Italian movie, Il Postino, into an opera. He was working at the University of Texas at Austin on a new opera based on the Frank Capra movie, Meet John Doe."	"Daniel Catán (April 3, 1949 – April 9, 2011) was a Mexican composer, writer and professor known particularly for his operas and his contribution of the Spanish language to the international repertory.With a compositional style described as lush, romantic and lyrical, Catán’s second opera, Rappaccini’s Daughter, became the first Mexican opera in the United States to be produced by a professional opera company.  Upon receiving international recognition, Catán’s next opera, Florencia en el Amazonas, became the first opera in Spanish to be commissioned by an opera company in the United States.  Shortly after, Catán received a Plácido Domingo Award and a Guggenheim Fellowship Award for his contributions to music.  In 2004, Catán’s opera Salsipuedes: a Tale of Love, War and Anchovies was premiered by the Houston Grand Opera.  In September 2010, his opera Il Postino was premiered by the Los Angeles Opera with Plácido Domingo singing as Pablo Neruda, a role written specifically for him.  Catán died while working on his next opera, Meet John Doe.Catán’s works also include vocal, chamber, orchestral and choral music as well as music for ballet, film and TV."	61
Blue eyed soul	Blue Eyed Soul is a term used to describe Soul and R&B music sung by white people. The term was first used in the 1960s about white artists performing music which was similar to the music being performed by Motown artists. It is sometimes called white soul.	"Blue-eyed soul (also known as white soul) is rhythm and blues and soul music performed by white artists.  The term was coined in the mid-1960s, to describe white artists who performed soul and R&B that was similar to the music of the Motown and Stax record labels.  Though many rhythm and blues radio stations in the United States in that period would only play music by black musicians, some began to play music by white acts considered to have ""soul feeling"" and their music was then described as ""blue-eyed soul""."	62
Monte dei Paschi di Siena	"Banca Monte dei paschi di Siena (sometimes referred to as BMPS or MPS) claims to be the oldest surviving retail bank in the world. It has its headquarters in Siena, Italy."	"Banca Monte dei Paschi di Siena S.p.A. (Italian pronunciation: [ˈbaŋka ˈmonte dei ˈpaski di ˈsjɛːna]), known as BMPS or just MPS, is an Italian bank. Tracing its history to a mount of piety founded in 1472 (548 years ago) and founded in its present form in 1624 (396 years ago), it is the world's oldest or second oldest bank, depending on the definition, and the fourth largest Italian commercial and retail bank.In 1995 the bank, then known as Monte dei Paschi di Siena, was transformed from a statutory corporation to a limited company called Banca Monte dei Paschi di Siena (Banca MPS). The Fondazione Monte dei Paschi di Siena was created to continue the charitable functions of the bank and to be, until the bailout in 2013, its largest single shareholder. Today Banca MPS has approximately 2,000 branches, 26,000 employees and 5.1 million customers in Italy, as well as branches and businesses abroad. A subsidiary, MPS Capital Services, handles corporate and investment banking.According to a research by Mediobanca and a press release by Banco BPM, Banco BPM overtook BMPS as the third largest commercial banking group in Italy in terms of total assets on 31 December 2016, after Banco BPM's formal formation on 1 January 2017. In 2016–17, BMPS was struggling to avoid a collapse, and was bailed out again by the Italian government in July 2017."	63
Guebwiller	Guebwiller is a commune in the Haut-Rhin department in Grand Est of eastern France.	"Guebwiller (French: Guebwiller, pronounced [ɡebvilɛʁ]; Alsatian: Gàwiller [ˈkaːviləʁ]; German: Gebweiler) is a commune in the Haut-Rhin department in Grand Est currently in north-eastern France."	64
Natural scientists	"There are some sciences that are used to study nature. According to these sciences, the things that can be observed in nature follow certain rules. These rules are often unknown, and natural sciences are about finding them. They often use what is called the scientific method to do this."	"Natural science is a branch of science concerned with the description, prediction, and understanding of natural phenomena, based on empirical evidence from observation and experimentation. Mechanisms such as peer review and repeatability of findings are used to try to ensure the validity of scientific advances."	65
Morges	Morges is a city in the Swiss canton of Vaud. It is the capital of the district Morges.	"Morges (Latin: Morgiis, plural, probably ablative, else dative) is a municipality in the Swiss canton of Vaud and the seat of the district of Morges. It is located on Lake Geneva."	66
MTS Centre	"Bell MTS Place, originally known as True North Centre and later as MTS Centre, is a sports arena in Winnipeg, Manitoba, Canada. The arena opened on November 16, 2004, and is the current home to the Winnipeg Jets of the National Hockey League (NHL). The arena was originally known as True North Centre during planning but naming rights were bought by Manitoba Telecom Services (MTS). After Bell Canada purchased MTS in spring 2017, the arena was renamed effective that May 30.The arena has been home to the Manitoba Moose of the American Hockey League (AHL), the Jets' top minor-league team, two different times. The team first played there from 2004 to 2011 before moving to St. John's, Newfoundland and Labrador, and then returned to Winnipeg in 2015."	"Bell MTS Place is an indoor arena in downtown Winnipeg, Manitoba. The arena is the home of the National Hockey League's Winnipeg Jets and their American Hockey League affiliate, the Manitoba Moose.The arena stands on the former Eaton's site and is owned and operated by True North Sports & Entertainment. The 440,000 square feet (41,000 m2) building was constructed at a cost of $133.5 million CAD. It opened on November 16, 2004, replacing the since-demolished Winnipeg Arena. It has a capacity of 15,321 for hockey and 16,345 for concerts."	67
Varna	Varna is a social concept from the Brahmin leaders of Hinduism in India	"Varna (Bulgarian: Варна, pronounced [ˈvarnɐ]) is the third-largest city in Bulgaria and the largest city and seaside resort on the Bulgarian Black Sea Coast. Situated strategically in the Gulf of Varna, the city has been a major economic, social and cultural centre for almost three millennia. Varna, historically known as Odessos (Ancient Greek: Ὀδησσός), grew from a Thracian seaside settlement to a major seaport on the Black Sea."	68
"Girard, Ohio"	"Girard is a city in Trumbull County, Ohio, United States. The population was 9,958 at the 2010 census. It is part of Mahoning Valley."	"Girard is a city in Trumbull County, Ohio, United States. The population was 9,958 at the 2010 census. It is part of the Youngstown-Warren-Boardman, OH-PA Metropolitan Statistical Area."	69
WWE World Championship	The WWE Championship is a professional wrestling world championship in WWE. It is the first world title of WWE. The title is said to be the biggest prize in professional wrestling and millions of people around the world watch matches for it.	"The WWE Championship is a world heavyweight championship created and promoted by the American professional wrestling promotion WWE, currently defended on their Raw brand. It is one of WWE's top three titles, alongside the Universal Championship on SmackDown and the NXT Championship on NXT. The current champion is Drew McIntyre, who is in his first reign."	70
Smartism	"Smartism is a sect of Hinduism in which, in contrast with Shaivism and Vaishnavism, one may worship multiple gods. It is often referred as a ""liberal"" sect and is passed along familial ties."	"Smarta tradition (स्मार्त) is a movement in Hinduism that developed during its classical period around the beginning of the Common Era. It reflects a Hindu synthesis of four philosophical strands: Mimamsa, Advaita, Yoga, and theism. The Smarta tradition rejects theistic sectarianism, and it is notable for the domestic worship of five shrines with five deities, all treated as equal – Shiva, Vishnu, Surya, Ganesha, and Shakti. The Smarta tradition contrasted with the older Shrauta tradition, which was based on elaborate rituals and rites. There has been considerable overlap in the ideas and practices of the Smarta tradition with other significant historic movements within Hinduism, namely Shaivism, Brahmanism, Vaishnavism, and Shaktism.The Smarta tradition is aligned with Advaita Vedanta, and regards Adi Shankara as its founder or reformer. Shankara championed that the ultimate reality is impersonal and Nirguna (attributeless) and that any symbolic god serves the same equivalent purpose. Inspired by this belief, the Smarta tradition followers, along with the five Hindu gods include a sixth impersonal god in their practice. The tradition has been called by William Jackson as ""advaitin, monistic in its outlook"".The term Smarta also refers to Brahmins who specialize in the Smriti corpus of texts named the Grihya Sutras, in contrast to Shrauta Sutras. Smarta Brahmins with their focus on the Smriti corpus, contrast from Srauta Brahmins who specialize in the Sruti corpus, that is rituals and ceremonies that follow the Vedas."	71
Lilly Singh	"Lilly Singh (born 26 September 1988) is a Canadian YouTuber, vlogger, comedian, writer and actress. She is mostly known by her YouTube username IISuperwomanII."	"Lilly Singh (born September 26, 1988) is a Canadian YouTuber, comedian, talk show host, writer, and actress, who initially gained fame on social media under the pseudonym IISuperwomanII. Born and raised in Scarborough, Ontario, Singh began making YouTube videos in 2010. By 2017, she was ranked tenth on the Forbes list of the world's highest paid YouTube stars, earning a reported $10.5 million; as of September 2019 she has fourteen million subscribers and over three billion video views. Singh has featured in the annual YouTube Rewind every year since 2014 (except for 2019). Forbes named her one of the 40 most powerful people in comedy in 2019. Singh has received an MTV Fandom Award, four Streamy Awards, two Teen Choice Awards, and a People's Choice Award."	72
Pyotr Deynekin	"Pyotr Stepanovich Deynekin (14 December 1937 – 19 August 2017) was a Soviet-Russian general. He was born in Morozovsk, Russia. In 1997, he was awarded the Hero of the Russian Federation."	"Pyotr Stepanovich Deynekin (14 December 1937 – 19 August 2017) was a Russian military general. He was born in Morozovsk, Russia. In 1997, he was awarded the Hero of the Russian Federation.Deynekin's rank was General of the army."	73
Alfonso Azpiri	"Alfonso Azpiri (1947 – August 18, 2017) was a Spanish comic book artist, whose work was mainly of the adult variety. He was born in Madrid. His work has been translated and published in a number of magazines, including Heavy Metal and Penthouse Comix. "	"Alfonso Azpiri Mejía (17 January 1947 − August 18, 2017) was a Spanish comic book artist, whose work was mainly of the adult variety."	74
Duncan Russell	"Duncan Russell (12 March 1958 – 18 August 2017) was an English football manager. He was born in London, England. He was the manager of Conference National side Mansfield Town until 12 May 2011 when they decided not to renew his contract.Russell died in London of liver cancer on 18 August 2017 at the age of 59."	Duncan Russell (12 March 1958 – 18 August 2017) was an English football manager who was in charge of Conference National side Mansfield Town and Hucknall Town.	75
Janusz Głowacki	"Janusz Głowacki (13 September 1938 – 19 August 2017) was a Polish-American playwright, essayist and screenwriter. He was born in Poznań, Poland. "	"Janusz Andrzej Głowacki (13 September 1938 – 19 August 2017), better known as Janusz Głowacki or colloquially simply as Głowa, was a Polish playwright, essayist and screenwriter. Głowacki was the recipient of multiple awards and honours, including Guggenheim Fellowship, two Nike Award nominations and BAFTA Award nomination. He was awarded the Gloria Artis Gold Medal in 2005 for his contribution to Polish culture, and in 2014, the Commander's Cross of the Order of Polonia Restituta."	76
Sonny Burgess	"Albert Austin ""Sonny"" Burgess (May 28, 1929 – August 18, 2017) was an American rockabilly guitarist and singer. He was born in Newport, Arkansas. He was known for working with fellow country musician D. J. Fontana. He gained popularity in Europe during most of his career. Burgess was inducted into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame of Europe in 1999."	"Albert Austin ""Sonny"" Burgess (May 28, 1929 – August 18, 2017) was an American rockabilly guitarist and singer."	77
D. J. Fontana	"Dominic Joseph ""D. J."" Fontana (March 15, 1931 – June 13, 2018) was an American musician. He was born in Shreveport, Louisiana. He was best known as the drummer for Elvis Presley for 14 years. He played on over 460 RCA cuts with Elvis. He also played for The Blue Moon Boys and Sonny Burgess. "	"Dominic Joseph Fontana (March 15, 1931 – June 13, 2018) was an American musician best known as the drummer for Elvis Presley for 14 years. In October 1954 he was hired to play drums for Presley, which marked the beginning of a fifteen-year relationship. He played on over 460 RCA cuts with Elvis."	78
Don Shepherd	"Donald John Shepherd (12 August 1927 – 18 August 2017) was a Welsh cricketer. He played for Glamorgan. One of the great county bowlers, he took more first-class wickets, 2,218 at 21.32 each, than any other player who never played Test cricket. He was born in Port Eynon, Glamorgan, Wales. "	"Donald John Shepherd (12 August 1927 – 18 August 2017) was a Welsh cricketer, who played for Glamorgan. One of the great county bowlers, he took more first-class wickets – 2,218 – than any other player who never played Test cricket."	79
Venero Mangano	"Venero Frank ""Benny Eggs"" Mangano (September 7, 1921 – August 18, 2017) was an American criminal. He was the underboss of the Genovese crime family. Since boss Daniel ""Danny the Lion"" Leo was imprisoned in 2007, Mangano was the family's senior leader outside prison. The nickname ""Benny Eggs"" came from his mother running an egg farm. He was released from prison on November 2, 2006, after serving a 15-year sentence for extortion."	"Venero Frank ""Benny Eggs"" Mangano (September 7, 1921 – August 18, 2017) was the underboss of the Genovese crime family. Since boss Daniel ""Danny the Lion"" Leo was imprisoned in 2007, Mangano was the family's senior leader outside prison. The nickname ""Benny Eggs"" was due to an egg store his mother had run. He was released on November 2, 2006, after serving a 15-year sentence for extortion and conspiracy."	80
Dominick Cirillo	"Dominick Vincent ""Quiet Dom"" Cirillo (born July 4, 1929) is an American gangster. He is a high-ranking member of the Genovese crime family, who briefly served as acting boss for the imprisoned Boss Vincent ""Chin"" Gigante. He was born in Harlem, New York. "	"Dominick V. ""Quiet Dom"" Cirillo (born July 4, 1929 in East Harlem) is a high-ranking member of the Genovese crime family, who briefly served as acting boss for the imprisoned Boss Vincent ""Chin"" Gigante."	81
Roger Pinto Molina	"Roger Pinto Molina (23 April 1960 – 16 August 2017) was a Bolivian right-wing politician. Pinto was born in Santa Rosa, Beni. He was elected to the Chamber of Deputies in 1997, from the single-member constituency 67 in Pando (covering areas in the provinces Nicolás Suárez, Manuripi and General Federico Román) as a Nationalist Democratic Action (ADN) candidate."	Roger Pinto Molina (23 April 1960 – 16 August 2017) was a Bolivian right-wing politician.	82
Lucien N. Nedzi	"Lucien Norbert Nedzi (born May 28, 1925) is a Democratic Party member of the United States House of Representatives from the State of Michigan."	"Lucien Norbert Nedzi (born May 28, 1925) is a former Democratic member of the United States House of Representatives from the State of Michigan.  Nedzi is of Polish descent."	83
Weston E. Vivian	"Weston ""Wes"" Edward Vivian (born October 25, 1924) is a Canadian-born American politician and retired engineer. He served as a member of the United States House of Representatives for Michigan's 2nd congressional district from January 3, 1965 through January 3, 1967. He was a member of the Democratic Party."	"Weston ""Wes"" Edward Vivian (born October 25, 1924) is a former politician from the U.S. state of Michigan."	84
Philip Ruppe	"Philip Edward Ruppe (born September 29, 1926) is an American politician. He is a member of the Republican Party. He served in the U.S. House of Representatives from 1967 to 1979 before running, unsuccessfully for the United States Senate in 1982. "	"Philip Edward Ruppe (born September 29, 1926) is a former politician from the U.S. state of Michigan and a member of the Republican Party. He served in the U.S. House of Representatives from 1967 to 1979 before running, unsuccessfully for the United States Senate in 1982. He is a Korean War veteran, having served as a lieutenant in the U.S. Navy. After leaving the U.S. House, Ruppe became active in business before running for election, without success, to the 103rd Congress."	85
Dale Kildee	"Dale Edward Kildee (born September 16, 1929) is an American politician. He was a U.S. Representative from Michigan, serving from 1977 until 2013. He is a member of the Democratic Party. "	"Dale Edward Kildee (born September 16, 1929) is a retired U.S. Representative from Michigan, serving from 1977 until 2013. He is a member of the Democratic Party."	86
Colin Meads	"Sir Colin Earl Meads (3 June 1936 – 20 August 2017) was a New Zealand rugby union player, coach and manager. He was born in Cambridge, New Zealand. He played 55 test matches (133 total games), most frequently in the lock forward position, for New Zealand's national team, the All Blacks, from 1957 until 1971."	"Sir Colin Earl Meads  (3 June 1936 – 20 August 2017) was a New Zealand rugby union player. He played 55 test matches (133 games), most frequently in the lock forward position, for New Zealand's national team, the All Blacks, from 1957 until 1971."	87
Sirkka Selja	"Sirkka Selja (20 March 1920 – 17 August 2017) was a Finnish poet and writer. She was born in Koski Hl, nowadays Hollola, Finland. Her real name was Sirkka-Liisa Tulonen."	"Sirkka Selja (20 March 1920 – 17 August 2017) was a Finnish poet and writer. She was born in Hämeenkoski, Finland. Her real name was Sirkka-Liisa Tulonen."	88